[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 6, "question": "How many people do you absolutely, 100 percent trust?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", ",", "CD", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 7, "answer": "Throwing yourself a party and get yourself a really nice gown.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["100 percent"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Oprah Winfrey"]}, "docId": "110117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "``", "NNP", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 18, "question": "Do you ever?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 19, "answer": "I don't do \"Bloody hell, I'm Oprah Winfrey.\"", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 34, "question": "Did you really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 35, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "WP", "PDT", "IN", "DT", "RB", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 48, "question": "What does it mean to you to actually have a network in your own name?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "TO", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 49, "answer": "I would have to say it is really difficult for me still to wrap my brain around what all of that really means.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 79, "question": "Why are you pushing for me to do this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 80, "answer": "We had a seduction through e-mail.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 82, "question": "How many people do you absolutely, 100 percent trust?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", ",", "CD", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 83, "answer": "Probably five.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["100 percent"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 84, "question": "Who would they be?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 85, "answer": "I'm not naming them.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 86, "question": "Can I guess?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 87, "answer": "You can guess.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 93, "question": "Are they people that we would know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 94, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Australia"]}, "docId": "110117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 129, "question": "How did she react to what you were saying?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 130, "answer": "Gayle didn't see it until we were actually in Australia.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 144, "question": "Go along with the program?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 145, "answer": "Could you just touch me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 162, "question": "Did you just say running a ship?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 163, "answer": "A newspaper is quite like a ship.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBP", "CD", "NNS", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 169, "question": "Did he just say?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 170, "answer": "There are two people I would never swear in front of.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 178, "question": "Do like being famous?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "VBG", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 179, "answer": "That's a good question, provocative question.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "VBZ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 223, "question": "You don't like cricket?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 224, "answer": "Cricket is fine.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 227, "question": "You were talking about Australia?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 228, "answer": "We went there.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Australia"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["John"]}, "docId": "110117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 239, "question": "How do you beat that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 240, "answer": "Actually it was not piloted by John.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "EX", "."], "qSentId": 254, "question": "Spiritual moment?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 255, "answer": "No, don't go there.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 266, "question": "Are you a tough boss?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 267, "answer": "No, I'm not a tough boss.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 272, "question": "Might you define your definition of \"tough\"?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "``", "IN", "''", "."], "aSentId": 273, "answer": "I suppose demanding.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJS", "IN", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "TO", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 283, "question": "Where would you say you're tough?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 284, "answer": "I would say that I'm tough in that I'm always looking for the best in myself and I want you to also present that for yourself and for the overall goal that we share if you are working for me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "."], "qSentId": 307, "question": "One-hundred?", "question_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "."], "aSentId": 308, "answer": "One-hundred.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 315, "question": "You don't like losing though, do you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "VBG", "IN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 316, "answer": "It's OK.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJR", "``", "NNS", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "VBG", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 336, "question": "What's been one of the most hurtful things you've had to hear or read about yourself?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "CD", "IN", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 337, "answer": "More \"Piers Morgan Tonight\" coming up.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 343, "question": "ORGAN: I know you hate this phrase but what is your brand do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "CC", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 344, "answer": "I'm the love brand.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 346, "question": "Aren't we all, darling?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "PRP", "DT", ",", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 347, "answer": "I'm of love brand.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 348, "question": "You like to shower love around?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "JJR", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 349, "answer": "That's really what it is.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 357, "question": "How many times have you been properly in love?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 358, "answer": "Boy, you're good.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 370, "question": "By properly do you mean was it really love?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 371, "answer": "Where it hurts your heart.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 378, "question": "You had your heart broken three times?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "VBN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 379, "answer": "Only two.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "RP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 380, "question": "ORGAN: Who are they?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 381, "answer": "I'm not naming them so they can call me up tomorrow.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "RB", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 388, "question": "I was just curious -- as you say your brand is love, when it doesn't work and you love somebody passionately and it just doesn't happen for whatever reason, how did you feel about that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "RB", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NN", "NN", ",", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 389, "answer": "When I look back to the relationship that I thought that really broke my heart, I was keeping a journal then.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 395, "question": "Do you really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 396, "answer": "Yes, I do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 397, "question": "Do you have them all?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 398, "answer": "I have them all.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 399, "question": "Why have you kept them?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 400, "answer": "I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 402, "question": "Do you still read them?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 403, "answer": "No, I haven't read them in years.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 410, "question": "What else have you got in there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 411, "answer": "That's about it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 413, "question": "INFREY: What about him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "WP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 414, "answer": "I tell you who he reminds me of.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Duke of Edinburgh"], "PERSON": ["Phillip"]}, "docId": "110117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 415, "question": "Who?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "."], "aSentId": 416, "answer": "The Duke of Edinburgh, Prince Phillip.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 417, "question": "Oh, really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 418, "answer": "Yes, really.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["$20,000"]}, "docId": "110117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "WP", "VBD", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "NNS", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "$", "CD", "VBD", "VBN", "PRP", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 435, "question": "So when was that moment that you knew it was more than just a good relationship, it was special?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WRB", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "JJR", "IN", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 436, "answer": "I think actually I had been betrayed by somebody in my family who had gone to the tabloids for, you know, $20,000 had sold me out.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "VBD", "RB", "POS", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "CC", "NN", "RP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 448, "question": "You looked at him and thought, \"I love this man\"?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "VBD", ",", "``", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "''", "."], "aSentId": 449, "answer": "No, I looked at him and thought here's something who is willing to stand in and stand up for you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "``", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "''", "``", "NN", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 451, "question": "Do you ever argue?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 452, "answer": "INFREY: No because it's a waste of time, because I do the \"Oprah Show,\" \"excuse me, excuse you.\"", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 455, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 456, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 457, "question": "Have you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 458, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 462, "question": "You never had therapy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 463, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "POS", "NN", "CC", "NNP", "VBZ", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 469, "question": "I need it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 470, "answer": "No, but I'm saying I've never had a day's therapy and God knows I could have used some.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 474, "question": "I just kind of assumed you would have at some stage had therapy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "VBN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 475, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "."], "qSentId": 484, "question": "Who?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "."], "aSentId": 485, "answer": "You.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 533, "question": "Period?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 534, "answer": "I'm just not the marrying kind.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "VBP", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 543, "question": "I mean, you know all those presents you could have?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 544, "answer": "Oh, have a really nice party with the guest list and the seating on the table and all that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 558, "question": "ORGAN: Do you ever wish you'd been a mother?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 559, "answer": "No, no, not in that, I wish I'd been a mother way.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 572, "question": "Does any part of you ever wonder what would have happened if you'd had that child?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "JJR", "WP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 573, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 578, "question": "Did you really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 579, "answer": "Oh, for sure.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 583, "question": "Did you ever tell your father that you had been pregnant?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 584, "answer": "No, hid it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBG", "NN", "CC", "DT", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NN", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 594, "question": "Did you come close to doing that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "TO", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 595, "answer": "No, not -- you know, I did stupid things like, you know, drinking detergent and all that kind of crazy stuff that you do when you're trying to get attention, when you're really just trying to cry for help.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "RB", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "TO", ":"], "qSentId": 642, "question": "As someone who aspires to be a teacher -- and in many ways you are a teacher -- if you were giving an academic report on President Obama, what would you say, good and bad, pluses, minuses?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "WP", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", ":", "CC", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", ",", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", ",", "NNS", ",", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 643, "answer": "I couldn't because I haven't paid enough attention to the curriculum to --", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 648, "question": "At all?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 649, "answer": "I really do not.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 660, "question": "Will you play a hypothetical game with me?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 661, "answer": "Mm-hmm.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "RB", ",", "VBG", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJS", "IN", "PRP", "CC", ",", "RB", ",", "DT", "JJS", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 672, "question": "Where's your lane?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 673, "answer": "My lane is evolving the consciousness of people everywhere, getting people to see the best of themselves and, therefore, the best in other people.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 679, "question": "No?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "aSentId": 680, "answer": "Not at all.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "TO", ":", "IN", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 681, "question": "Who knows the American people better than you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "NNS", "JJR", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 682, "answer": "INFREY: Well, I might be in a position to talk to -- to be an adviser.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Harpo"]}, "docId": "110117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", ",", "CD", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 689, "question": "How many people do you employ?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 690, "answer": "Right now, 464 at Harpo.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 692, "question": "And it's a billion-dollar-plus business, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 693, "answer": "All the businesses.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 700, "question": "How do you get America back on its feet?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 701, "answer": "I don't know the answer to that.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 714, "question": "You still write all the checks?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 715, "answer": "I don't write all of them now.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["100,000 dollars"]}, "docId": "110117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "IN", "CD", "NNS", ",", "CC", "IN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 716, "question": "How many of them do you sign?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 717, "answer": "I sign all the checks that are over 100,000 dollars, and that's a lot of checks.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "JJ", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 719, "question": "How many?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 720, "answer": "INFREY: Oh, probably, you know, several hundred.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 721, "question": "Of over 100,000 dollars each?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 722, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["100,000 dollars"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "RBS", "JJ", "PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", ":", "CC", "PRP$", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 728, "question": "Do you feel pain?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 729, "answer": "The most pain I feel is -- and my accountants will tell you this.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 737, "question": "The one that's caused you most agony?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "CD", "WDT", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP", "JJS", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 738, "answer": "You're good.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 746, "question": "Are you worth that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 747, "answer": "I'm not sitting around counting it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 751, "question": "So how do you know without counting it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 752, "answer": "Because I already have counted it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["300 million dollars"]}, "docId": "110117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJR", "IN", "CD", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 757, "question": "Do you know how much?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 758, "answer": "No, I really don't, but I know it's more than 300 million dollars.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 759, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 760, "answer": "Yes, of course.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 768, "question": "Well, what do you think of the old saying, you know, money can't buy you happiness?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "VBG", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 769, "answer": "It can certainly pave the way for it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 780, "question": "Oprah, what is it you do best?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "PRP", "VBP", "JJS", "."], "aSentId": 781, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJR", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 792, "question": "Are you as happy now, do you think, as you've ever been?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", "RB", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 793, "answer": "I'm happier than I've ever been.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["January 17"]}, "docId": "110117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 808, "question": "Oh, is it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 809, "answer": "January 17.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 817, "question": "Why would you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 818, "answer": "INFREY: I would because I hold him in reverence.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 840, "question": "How have I done?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 841, "answer": "I -- you have been surprising.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110117pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 842, "question": "Surprisingly bad?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 843, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]